Get unlimited CLE for 12 months — Only $99 per month! [Subscribe Today](https://www.nbi-sems.com/cart/checkout/AddSubToCart?altid=00001SUB&cpn=CLEPASSWB&mp=1)

[(800) 930-6182](tel:+18009306182 "Call (800) 930-6182")

[National Business Institute

NBI Homepage](https://www.nbi-sems.com/ "NBI Homepage")

* [National Business Institute
    
    NBI Homepage](https://www.nbi-sems.com/ "NBI Homepage")
* Resources

* Unlimited CLE

* Search  Submit

Primary Navigation
------------------

* Resources
* Unlimited CLE

1. [Home](https://www.nbi-sems.com/)
2. Privacy Policy

NBI Privacy Policy
==================

* * *

**Last Updated:** March 20, 2023

NBI, Inc., ("NBI", "we" or "us") is a non-profit 501(c)(3) organization which provides practical, skill-based continuing legal education ("CLE") and other continuing education seminars and online courses. NBI operates two websites [www.nbi-sems.com](http://www.nbi-sems.com/) and [ipe.nbi-sems.com](http://ipe.nbi-sems.com/) (each a " Site" and collectively the "Sites").

NBI respects the privacy of your Personal Information. We have developed this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to describe the categories of Personal Information we collect, the purposes for collection and with whom we share Personal Information.

**Updates:** We may update this Policy from time to time (see Section 13) so please check this Policy periodically for updates.

**Alternative Format.** If you need access to this Policy in an alternative format, please contact us by any of the methods listed in Section 14.

1\. What is Personal Information?
---------------------------------

Personal Information, for purposes of this Policy, means information which alone or in combination can be used to identify or locate a natural person.

Personal Information excludes: (i) information which is lawfully publicly available; or (ii) de-identified or aggregated data which can no longer be used to identify you.

2\. Categories of Personal Information We Collect
-------------------------------------------------

We collect the following categories of Personal Information.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Category** | **Examples** |
| **Identifiers** | Name  <br>Home address  <br>Business address  <br>Email address  <br>Telephone number  <br>Bar ID  <br>IP Address  <br>Year of Bar Admission  <br>States of Bar Admission |
| **Customer Service Information** | Financial information such as credit and debit card numbers for products or services, which is processed using a third party payment processor. |
| **Commercial Information** | History of your orders for products and services.<br><br>Attendance history at events or online presentations. |
| **Internet Data** | IP Address  <br>Device identifier  <br>Operating system  <br>Browser type  <br>Network information |
| **Geolocation Data** | Imprecise geolocation |
| **Employment Information** | Previous Employment  <br>Current Employer  <br>Resume information |
| **Education Information** | Schools attended  <br>Dates of Graduation  <br>Degree information |

3\. Sources of Personal Information We Collect
----------------------------------------------

We collect information, including your Personal Information, from the following sources:

**_A. Information You Provide to Us Directly_**

We collect Personal Information directly from you when you create an account, register for a course, purchase products or services, request a quote, communicate with us, or otherwise provide your information to us.

**_B. Information We Collect Automatically_**

When you use the Sites, we may automatically collect certain information, including:

* **Usage Details** - Details of your access to and use of the Sites, including traffic data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on or through the Sites. We may also collect the webpage from which you came immediately before reaching the Sites and the webpage to which you went immediately after leaving the Sites.
* **Device Information** -Information from your devices as described under Internet Data above.

**_C. Information We Receive from Third Party Sources_**

We may also receive Personal Information about you from other sources, such as from third party mailing lists, social media platforms and publicly available sources. At this time, we only use mailing lists provided by third parties for direct mail and email purposes.

We may obtain information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services when you visit our Sites using Cookies. See Section 7 for information on mechanisms that enable consumers to exercise choice about targeted advertising.

The Sites may allow you to provide information to be published or displayed on public areas of the Sites or transmitted to other users of the Sites or third parties. We may collect this Personal Information about you from your posts or the posts of other users.

4\. How We Use Your Personal Information
----------------------------------------

We may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Purpose of Collection and Use** | **Examples** |
| **To Communicate with You** | To respond to your communications and answer your questions.<br><br>To notify you when we update this Policy.<br><br>To notify you of changes to any products or services we offer.<br><br>To notify you of CLE opportunities. |
| **Customer Service** | To respond to your requests for a price quote.<br><br>To provide you with support.<br><br>To respond to your inquiries.<br><br>To monitor and improve our responses. |
| **Account Creation and Maintenance** | To create, maintain, customize, and secure your account.<br><br>To provide support for your account. |
| **Ordering** | To process and fulfill your orders.<br><br>To provide price quotes.<br><br>To facilitate new product orders.<br><br>To process your payments.<br><br>To prevent transactional fraud.<br><br>To deliver orders or process returns. |
| **Reporting to Accreditation Agencies** | To verify individual attendance of our live or web produced events, with your permission, upon request from authorized accreditation agencies. |
| **Operations** | To operate our Sites.<br><br>To process job applications.<br><br>To run our organization.<br><br>For administrative purposes. |
| **Analytics** | To store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize the Sites according to your individual interests.<br><br>To help us market, sell, and provide information about our products and services to you.<br><br>To improve our services, course offerings and online advertising. |
| **To Improve our Products and Services** | For testing, research, course development, analysis, support and product development.<br><br>To develop, support and improve the Sites and our course offerings, products and services.<br><br>To recognize you when you visit the Site. |
| **Marketing and Advertising** | To deliver content and product and service offerings relevant to your interests.<br><br>To engage in targeted advertising.<br><br>To send you offers via email, mail or text message.<br><br>To understand and anticipate your needs and preferences. |
| **Site Management** | To ensure the Sites are of interest to you (including, customization of advertising and content).<br><br>To help us better understand your use of the Sites.<br><br>To help maintain the safety, security, and integrity of the Sites, as well as our data, products, services, databases, other technology assets, and business. |
| **Compliance and Legal Purposes** | To carry out our legal obligations.<br><br>To enforce our legal rights or the rights of others.<br><br>To comply with law enforcement requests and legal process.<br><br>To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection. |

5\. When We Share Personal Information
--------------------------------------

We may share Personal Information with certain third parties for the reasons set forth below:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Entity or person with whom we share your Personal Information** | **Purpose** |
| **Service Providers** | To provide content, product and services to us.<br><br>To provide IT services and secure our IT network.<br><br>To engage in marketing and advertising.<br><br>To communicate with you.<br><br>To provide support for the operations of our business. |
| **Payment Processors** | NBI accepts but does not directly collect credit card or other payment information via the Sites.<br><br>If you make a purchase through the Sites, your payment and payment information will be processed by our payment processor, PayPal. Purchases made on or through the Sites, as well as any payment information provided in connection with purchases made on or through the Sites will also be subject to PayPal's privacy policy and other terms. For more information on PayPal and how payment information processed by PayPal will be treated, please see: [https://www.paypal.com/myaccount/privacy/privacyhub](https://www.paypal.com/myaccount/privacy/privacyhub). |
| **Ad Tech Companies** | To help us serve targeted advertising to you.<br><br>To assist in analyzing our marketing and advertising efforts.<br><br>To market, sell, and provide information about our courses, products and services to you. |
| **Other Users of the Sites** | To respond to a third party’s claim that content on our Site violates the DMCA or Terms of Use. |
| **Parties to Transactions** | To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information held by us about our customers or employees is among the assets transferred. |
| **Professional Advisors** | To seek advice regarding operation of our business.<br><br>To enforce our legal rights. |
| **Government Authorities** | To respond to law enforcement requests.<br><br>To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.<br><br>If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of NBI, our customers, employees or others. |

6\. Cookies and Related Technologies
------------------------------------

When you visit the Sites, we use certain cookies and other tracking technologies provided by third parties to collect information about you. We use these technologies to operate the website, to perform analytics, to provide you with interest-based advertising or other targeted content and to improve our Site.

The information collected through the use of cookies and other tracking technologies may be associated with your Personal Information or they may collect information, including Personal Information, about your online activities over time and across different websites, apps, and other online services websites. To learn more about how we use cookies, please visit our [Cookie Policy](https://www.nbi-sems.com/cookie-policy).

**Do Not Track.** At this time, the Sites do not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, such as "do-not-track" instructions.

7\. Privacy Choices
-------------------

We strive to provide you with and inform you of choices regarding your information, including your Personal Information. This Section 7 describes mechanisms for you to control certain uses and disclosures of your Personal Information.

* **Tracking Technologies** - You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies or block the use of other tracking technologies, some parts of the Sites may be inaccessible or not function properly.
* **Location Information** - You can choose whether or not to allow the Sites to collect and use real-time information about your device's location through the device's privacy settings. If you block the use of location information, some parts of the Sites may be inaccessible or not function properly.
* **Promotion by NBI** - If you do not want us to use your email address to promote our products or services, you can opt-out here: [https://www.nbi-sems.com/Unsubscribe](https://www.nbi-sems.com/Unsubscribe). You can also always opt-out by logging into the Sites and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an email stating your request to [customerservice@nbi-sems.com.](mailto:customerservice@nbi-sems.com "mailto:customerservice@nbi-sems.com")

For information on accessing or correcting your Personal Information which we hold, please see Section 9.

8\. Children's Privacy
----------------------

The Sites are not directed to nor intended for use by anyone under eighteen (18) years of age ("Prohibited Users"). We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from Prohibited Users. No Prohibited Users may use the Sites. If you are a Prohibited User, do not use or provide any Personal Information to, on, or through the Sites.

If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a Prohibited User, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a Prohibited User, please contact us by any of the methods listed in Section 14.

9\. Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information
------------------------------------------------------

You can review and change your Personal Information by logging into the Sites and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send us an email at [customerservice@nbi-sems.com](mailto:customerservice@nbi-sems.com "mailto:customerservice@nbi-sems.com") to update any Personal Information that you have provided to us.

If you have created an account, you may close your account by sending a request to [customerservice@nbi-sems.com](mailto:customerservice@nbi-sems.com "mailto:customerservice@nbi-sems.com"). Upon request, we will work with you in terminating your account and to remove select information we have collected about you. However, please note that we may disassociate posted content and information from you in lieu of removing the same. Further, not all information can be deleted such as information which has been aggregated or is archived. We may also retain select information to prevent, investigate or identify any wrongdoing in connection with the Sites or to satisfy other legal obligations.

10\. Notices for Individuals Located Outside the United States
--------------------------------------------------------------

We do not market to customers outside the United States and the Sites are not directed to persons outside the United States. Any information collected through the Sites as described in this Policy will be stored in the United States or any other country in which NBI or its service providers maintain facilities. If you are located outside of the United States, please note that we may transfer information, including Personal Information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.

11\. Privacy Notice for California Residents
--------------------------------------------

California's "Shine the Light" law (Cal. Civil Code § 1798.83) permits customers who are California residents to request information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not currently disclose Personal Information of California residents to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. For questions, please contact us as described in Section 14 below.

12\. Data Security
------------------

We have implemented reasonable technical, physical and administrative safeguards designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access or acquisition.

13\. Changes to this Policy
---------------------------

We may update this Policy from time to time. If we make changes to this Policy, we will post the updated Policy on this page with a notice showing the date that this Policy was last updated or otherwise provide notice to you. The dates this Policy was last reviewed and last modified are identified at the top of the page. We recommend that you periodically visit the Sites to check for any changes.

14\. How to Contact Us
----------------------

To ask questions or comment about this Policy and our privacy practices, you may contact us at:

**Phone:** 1-800-930-6182

**Email:** [customerservice@nbi-sems.com](mailto:customerservice@nbi-sems.com "mailto:customerservice@nbi-sems.com")

**Postal Address:**

NBI, Inc  
Attn: Customer Service  
PO Box 3067  
Eau Claire, WI 54702

If you need to access this Policy in an alternative format, please contact us by one of the methods described above.

Supplementary Navigation
------------------------

    Get to Know Us
* Shop & Learn
* Resources for You
* Let Us Help You
* Connect with Us:[](https://www.linkedin.com/company/national-business-institute-nbi-inc.-/ "Linkedin")[](https://www.facebook.com/NBICLE/ "Facebook")[](https://twitter.com/NBICLE "Twitter")

Connect with Us:

© 2024 - National Business Institute

This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience. We use this information in order to improve and customize your browsing experience, in addition to improving our internal analytics and metrics about our visitors. To find out more about the cookies we use, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.nbi-sems.com/cookie-policy "View Cookie Policy").

Accept
